[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "You OK?", "question_tokens": ["You", "OK", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "It's also miraculous that our tent didn't just fly away.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "also", "miraculous", "that", "our", "tent", "did", "n't", "just", "fly", "away", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "What do you think when you see this photo?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "when", "you", "see", "this", "photo", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "Beauty.", "answer_tokens": ["Beauty", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "What was she like in high school?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "she", "like", "in", "high", "school", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "Smiling all the time.", "answer_tokens": ["Smiling", "all", "the", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "How did Krystle make you feel?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "Krystle", "make", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "NNP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "Oh, full heart, my whole heart and soul.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "full", "heart", ",", "my", "whole", "heart", "and", "soul", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Krystle"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 99, "question": "What kind of young woman did she become?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "young", "woman", "did", "she", "become", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "AMPBELL: Smart.", "answer_tokens": ["AMPBELL", ":", "Smart", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "Lots of friends?", "question_tokens": ["Lots", "of", "friends", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "Oh, lots of friends.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "lots", "of", "friends", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "What did that mean to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "that", "mean", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "Oh, everything.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "everything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "CC", "NN", "PRP$", "CC", "NN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "What do you think when you see her there?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "when", "you", "see", "her", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "I wish I could go up and grab her and kiss her.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "wish", "I", "could", "go", "up", "and", "grab", "her", "and", "kiss", "her", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "How do you make sense of this?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "make", "sense", "of", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "I don't.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 146, "question": "You can't believe something that something like this would happen to someone you love?", "question_tokens": ["You", "ca", "n't", "believe", "something", "that", "something", "like", "this", "would", "happen", "to", "someone", "you", "love", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "WDT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "TO", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 147, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "And what do you know about the condition, first of all, of poor Martin's mother and his sister?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "do", "you", "know", "about", "the", "condition", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "of", "poor", "Martin", "'s", "mother", "and", "his", "sister", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "Martin was a great kid.", "answer_tokens": ["Martin", "was", "a", "great", "kid", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Martin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "Do you know any more about their condition?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "any", "more", "about", "their", "condition", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "RBR", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "I haven't heard.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "n't", "heard", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 217, "question": "Caitlin, how did you hear about what had happened?", "question_tokens": ["Caitlin", ",", "how", "did", "you", "hear", "about", "what", "had", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "I had seen from another good friend of mine that she had called me and told me.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "had", "seen", "from", "another", "good", "friend", "of", "mine", "that", "she", "had", "called", "me", "and", "told", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Richard", "Denise", "Martin", "Jane"], "LOCATION": ["Henry"]}, "docId": "130416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "IN", ",", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "TO", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "CC", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "Is that your take on the Richard family?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "your", "take", "on", "the", "Richard", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "Yes, the Richard family all around, from Denise to the father, Bill to Henry, Martin and Jane, they were always just so welcoming and kind, and I really enjoyed babysitting for them.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "the", "Richard", "family", "all", "around", ",", "from", "Denise", "to", "the", "father", ",", "Bill", "to", "Henry", ",", "Martin", "and", "Jane", ",", "they", "were", "always", "just", "so", "welcoming", "and", "kind", ",", "and", "I", "really", "enjoyed", "babysitting", "for", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Richard"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "What was the vigil like?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "vigil", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "The vigil was amazing.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "vigil", "was", "amazing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Senate", "Piers"], "PERSON": ["Terry Gainor"]}, "docId": "130416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "What do we know?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "we", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "Well, at this point, we are told this is according to the Senate sergeant in arms, Terry Gainor, that the envelope did test positive today at the actual lab, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "at", "this", "point", ",", "we", "are", "told", "this", "is", "according", "to", "the", "Senate", "sergeant", "in", "arms", ",", "Terry", "Gainor", ",", "that", "the", "envelope", "did", "test", "positive", "today", "at", "the", "actual", "lab", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "Or has that already been ruled out?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "has", "that", "already", "been", "ruled", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "That's a great question.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "great", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "CC", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "What is your take on where this investigation may be going?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "take", "on", "where", "this", "investigation", "may", "be", "going", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "Well, I really do think we have to be patient and wait and see.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "really", "do", "think", "we", "have", "to", "be", "patient", "and", "wait", "and", "see", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FBI", "NSA"], "PERSON": ["Napolitano"]}, "docId": "130416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "Have you got any inside-track intelligence whatsoever that would hint at either of those two strands?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "got", "any", "inside-track", "intelligence", "whatsoever", "that", "would", "hint", "at", "either", "of", "those", "two", "strands", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "We had a initial briefing tonight by the director of the FBI as well as Secretary Napolitano and the director of the NSA.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "had", "a", "initial", "briefing", "tonight", "by", "the", "director", "of", "the", "FBI", "as", "well", "as", "Secretary", "Napolitano", "and", "the", "director", "of", "the", "NSA", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "Is there any realistic criticism that should be leveled to anyone here?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "any", "realistic", "criticism", "that", "should", "be", "leveled", "to", "anyone", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "Well, I certainly wouldn't do that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "certainly", "would", "n't", "do", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "What is your view of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "CHIFF: Well, I think it is -- I think it's very smart of them.", "answer_tokens": ["CHIFF", ":", "Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "is", "--", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "very", "smart", "of", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "From everything that you've seen and read, do you see real signs that this is more likely to be some form of domestic extremist attack?", "question_tokens": ["From", "everything", "that", "you", "'ve", "seen", "and", "read", ",", "do", "you", "see", "real", "signs", "that", "this", "is", "more", "likely", "to", "be", "some", "form", "of", "domestic", "extremist", "attack", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RBR", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "Well, honestly, Piers, I'm not sure that we know that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "honestly", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "sure", "that", "we", "know", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "From what you've seen and read, where is your head going with this?", "question_tokens": ["From", "what", "you", "'ve", "seen", "and", "read", ",", "where", "is", "your", "head", "going", "with", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "VB", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "Well, there are a couple of observations I have, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "are", "a", "couple", "of", "observations", "I", "have", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 386, "question": "Can you see these pictures, Bob?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "see", "these", "pictures", ",", "Bob", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 387, "answer": "No, I can't see them.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "ca", "n't", "see", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bob Baer", "Mark"]}, "docId": "130416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "What do you make of the way the investigation is unfurling here?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "the", "way", "the", "investigation", "is", "unfurling", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "Piers, what I would say is actually I think the answer is something a little bit in the middle of your -- Bob Baer and Mark, what they're saying to you.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "what", "I", "would", "say", "is", "actually", "I", "think", "the", "answer", "is", "something", "a", "little", "bit", "in", "the", "middle", "of", "your", "--", "Bob", "Baer", "and", "Mark", ",", "what", "they", "'re", "saying", "to", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "Mark Potok, if it is a domestic terror attack, is it more likely, from your experience, to be a lone wolf or part of an existing group?", "question_tokens": ["Mark", "Potok", ",", "if", "it", "is", "a", "domestic", "terror", "attack", ",", "is", "it", "more", "likely", ",", "from", "your", "experience", ",", "to", "be", "a", "lone", "wolf", "or", "part", "of", "an", "existing", "group", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "Well, I think in general, it's more likely to be a lone wolf.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "in", "general", ",", "it", "'s", "more", "likely", "to", "be", "a", "lone", "wolf", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mark Potok"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "What would be the repercussions if, for argument's sake, it does turn out to be some sort of al Qaeda related attack in terms of the impact on countries like China who have been affected?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "be", "the", "repercussions", "if", ",", "for", "argument", "'s", "sake", ",", "it", "does", "turn", "out", "to", "be", "some", "sort", "of", "al", "Qaeda", "related", "attack", "in", "terms", "of", "the", "impact", "on", "countries", "like", "China", "who", "have", "been", "affected", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", ",", "IN", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VB", "RP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "Well, the Chinese have been the victims of al Qaeda in the weaker part of the country.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "Chinese", "have", "been", "the", "victims", "of", "al", "Qaeda", "in", "the", "weaker", "part", "of", "the", "country", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["China"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "Is that, do you think, how most people in Boston feel today?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "how", "most", "people", "in", "Boston", "feel", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "WRB", "RBS", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "Well, Piers, I think that when I wrote that, I probably was a little more despondent than I should've been.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "think", "that", "when", "I", "wrote", "that", ",", "I", "probably", "was", "a", "little", "more", "despondent", "than", "I", "should", "'ve", "been", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Boston"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "TO", "VB", ":", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "Is it one of not just resolution, but determination not to be beaten?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "one", "of", "not", "just", "resolution", ",", "but", "determination", "not", "to", "be", "beaten", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "CD", "IN", "RB", "RB", "NN", ",", "CC", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "Determination not to change our lifestyle, not to make -- not to give in to the intimidation that is at the heart of all terrorist acts.", "answer_tokens": ["Determination", "not", "to", "change", "our", "lifestyle", ",", "not", "to", "make", "--", "not", "to", "give", "in", "to", "the", "intimidation", "that", "is", "at", "the", "heart", "of", "all", "terrorist", "acts", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "CC", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "But once you realized what had happened, did you have any second thoughts, any doubts that you should go through with it?", "question_tokens": ["But", "once", "you", "realized", "what", "had", "happened", ",", "did", "you", "have", "any", "second", "thoughts", ",", "any", "doubts", "that", "you", "should", "go", "through", "with", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "Well, we were not going to cancel our wedding, but we did think about possibly postponing it or coming up with alternative plans.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "were", "not", "going", "to", "cancel", "our", "wedding", ",", "but", "we", "did", "think", "about", "possibly", "postponing", "it", "or", "coming", "up", "with", "alternative", "plans", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "Robert, obviously when you realized the scale of what had happened, after horror and devastation everywhere, did that make you even more determined to go through this, as Kelli said, to make sure the terrorist didn't win?", "question_tokens": ["Robert", ",", "obviously", "when", "you", "realized", "the", "scale", "of", "what", "had", "happened", ",", "after", "horror", "and", "devastation", "everywhere", ",", "did", "that", "make", "you", "even", "more", "determined", "to", "go", "through", "this", ",", "as", "Kelli", "said", ",", "to", "make", "sure", "the", "terrorist", "did", "n't", "win", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "RBR", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kelli"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "What do you make of the people or the person that did this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "the", "people", "or", "the", "person", "that", "did", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "Right now, you can't make sense of it.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "now", ",", "you", "ca", "n't", "make", "sense", "of", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]